Now, a bevel is actually a piece of clear glass that has been smoothed and polished down on it's sides.
So that it goes to a smaller width and it's thicker on the inside.
So, I wanted to show you, these are are some of the sipper bevels.
Sipper meaning that it's got this little circular motion going on, but it's got this iridized or dichroic acrylic glass, which is the different, how it picks up the different hues of the rainbow.
They've got them in the larger and the smaller.
There's also a granite dichroic bevels, which are these little; you can see that iridized, dichroic glass in the center of that bevel and on the bevel; actually, if you can get a close up of that, it's, you can see the levels of glass and how it's been polished to a raised surface.
There are also just clear sipper and regular bevel rectangular square.
You can find these in all different sizes and shapes.
And, I just wanted to let you know those are available to you out there.
They work really well to go around the border of some of your leaded and foiled projects, as well, to add an extra dimension and elegance to them.